[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "What year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "2016.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "That was lower?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "TIME": ["morning"]}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Isn't it obvious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "I'll tell you, if you give me equal man and woman, the difference is, if you watch a Saturday morning TV commercial, a woman -- a girl -- it's always four girls playing together, it's always one boy go, I won.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "But Suze, have you seen that women are much more reticent to ask for a raise than men?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Men, are you kidding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "We're the fixers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Is this dumb guy talking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "I don't think they decide it, but I think it can help them, it can enhance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "What do you -- when you say utility, what do you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Utility shows like \"The Doctors,\" should take home, shows like what Suze does where people could take something away.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Is that a relevant subject matter anymore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "I think there's always room for something good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 254, "question": "You know where I'm going with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "No, I know exactly --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "One guy and four women, something like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["ABC"]}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "I think she could be a huge -- look at what she did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ":", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "You're an ABC person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "You're going to the airport today, I say you don't have to take off your shoes, you go (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "I'm happy to take them off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "So here's the real question, how many women on this panel read that book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "I actual did for research.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "You do read it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Of course I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "But Serena, do you know what it's about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I know what it's about.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Serena"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Did you read it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "I know the basic premise.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Donny -- are you a spanker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "No, absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Is that intimidating to a lot of men?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I think it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Are you intimidated by me, Donny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "If you and I --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "You're gorgeous, so I'm curious, do you run into that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "How many years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "That's 59 years the way they care for each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "How do you live normal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "It's difficult but for me, I'm just normal individual.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "Why do we care?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "They're the royals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "Does that mean Serena, as a tennis star, does she have an obligation to young people to act a certain way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Serena"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Does Piers know we're here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Divorce is very painful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 742, "question": "Did you ever doubt yourself yesterday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 743, "answer": "I did, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 757, "question": "What was the turning point for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 758, "answer": "Believe it or not, very much the same is that an Orman never -- my mother always taught me that an Orman nerve gives up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "Where does this come from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "The common thing you both said it is came from your parents.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "When we come back, I'm going to ask each one of you what year will be our first female president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "That's easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "What year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "2016.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "Is that a Hillary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "Lara?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "I hope never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 819, "question": "Lara?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 820, "answer": "I think he did what he set out to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 830, "question": "Should he have stayed home?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 831, "answer": "I think for the party he should have stayed home, because I don't think it really helped in the long run.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 835, "question": "Do you guys think it damaged his brand at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 836, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 850, "question": "I think he was in a pizza place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 851, "answer": "That's awesome.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 854, "question": "Let's start with you, Serena?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 855, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Serena"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 867, "question": "Do you think that was staged?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "No, I'm just saying, when you see him at baseball games -- no, no, of course that was not staged.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 869, "question": "The question was, what would Mitt have done in that situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 870, "answer": "God, I have no idea what he would do there or in any situation, for that matter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RBR", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 917, "question": "Are you kidding me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 918, "answer": "OK, more lightning round, Suze.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 933, "question": "Suze?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 934, "answer": "Well, if you didn't know -- just on the surface, because this is -- who knows them, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120910pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 958, "question": "Serena?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 959, "answer": "I think each of the -- I'm going to give a politically correct answer, because I do know Kim and I think she's a great girl.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]